Today I got such a surprise that I was really
surprised.  So the day starts
with a call from mom that he is coming back from Amritsar.  I
quickly picked up Manya
because brother, it was important to clean the house.
Otherwise our class would have started.  Then a little
skin care.  I was trying this charcoal face mask for the
first time.  But the
experience was good.  Meanwhile the
bell rang outside and what I saw left me completely stunned.
Mom brought my Activa from Amritsar.
This is the best moment of my entire day.
Then I thought why not make this day a
little more special by going out for dinner.
I found a lovely
subscriber here.  Most of the time was spent thinking about
what to eat?  For dinner,
I had my favourite noodles and
Manchurian combo.  Finally, let's end the blog with this sweet dish.